princetonecom.com 2006-06-29

# Privacy

|  We are committed to protecting the privacy and information of our Web site users. To carry out this commitment, we have adopted this privacy policy to help protect your personal information. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of what information this Web site collects, how such information is used, and other related matters.

**Collection of Information**  
Our Web server automatically recognizes the Internet address (and specific domain) from which you are accessing our Web site. When you visit our site, we collect general information that does not identify you specifically but informs us of the pages visited, the areas of the Web site where you have spent the most time, and other Web sites you linked to while visiting our Web site. The above list is meant to be illustrative and not exclusive. This general information is only used in the aggregate so we can improve our services to you and other Web site users.

On certain Web pages, we will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. If you choose not to register or provide Personal Information, you can still use most of our Web site but you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

**How the Information is used**  
We will protect the confidentiality of any personal information you share with us. We will not sell or share your personal identifiable information with any third party except as required by law. In addition, in the event our business or assets are sold or acquired, the information you provided may become the property of the new owner.

We use the information collected in various ways, including but not limited to responding to any queries regarding our services, emailing you with updates to our services, and providing more efficient services as further described. If you wish not to receive email from us detailing our services or updates, please notify us. We take all the collected general information, compile and analyze all the data, and modify our Web site so it better serves our users' needs. As an example, if we find that the majority of our users tend to go to a certain portion of our Web site, we will move such portion of the Web site closer to the home page or create a link directly to that portion of the Web site. This type of modification to the Web site will make your visit more efficient.

**Tracking**  
We use cookies to help improve our services to you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Among other things, the cookie will help keep track of information you gave us so you will not have to reenter it each time you enter our Web site.

**Security**  
We use certain standard efforts to authenticate users of our Web site; however; our authentication relies upon the degree to which user ID's and passwords are adequately protected. We do not guarantee the absolute security of our Web site due to the nature of the Internet.

**Submitted Information**  
If a user of our Web site sends us any message or communication, such message or communication will become our property and will not be returned. We shall have the right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, distribute, and display such messages or communications, including the sender's name.

**Third Party Links**  
Our Web site permits you to link to third party Web sites. We do not endorse any information posted on such third party Web sites nor the reliability or authenticity of any such posted information. We do not have any relationship with such third party Web sites other than permitting you to directly link to them for your convenience. Such third party Web sites may be governed by their own rules and regulations and we advise that you read and adhere to such rules and regulations when visiting such third party Web sites. We will have no liability whatsoever for any of your actions on such third party Web sites nor will we be liable for any information or data downloaded by you or any transaction entered into by you while visiting such third party Web sites.

**Governing Law**  
This privacy policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of New Jersey without regard to conflicts of law provisions. You agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts of the State of New Jersey in any disputes concerning this Web site or any information you have provided.

**Modifications**  
We encourage you to review this privacy from time to time, as it may be amended or updated by us at any time. If you have any questions about this policy or any amendments or updates, contact us at:  
Princeton eCom Corporation  
650 College Road East  
Princeton, NJ 08540-6624  
Phone: (609) 606-3000  
Fax: (609) 606-3297  
Email: [legal@princetonecom.com](mailto:legal@princetonecom.com)

**Copyright Notices**  
The works of authorship contained in this World Wide Website, including but not limited to all design, text, sound recordings and images ("Site Content"), are owned, except as otherwise expressly stated by Princeton eCom Corporation. Except as otherwise expressly stated herein, Site Content may not be copied, transmitted, displayed, performed, distributed (for compensation or otherwise), licensed, altered, framed, stored for subsequent use or otherwise used in whole or in part in any manner without Princeton eCom's prior written consent, except to the extent permitted by the Copyright Act of 1976 (17 U.S.C. § 107), as amended, and then, only with notices of Princeton eCom's proprietary rights.

**Trademark Notices**  
Princeton eCom and [sm] symbol identified in this site are service marks of Princeton eCom Corporation. All other featured products or services in this sites are the trademarks of their respective owners.

|
